<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kaku</string>
    <string name="support_text">"Like Kaku? Rate the app!"</string>
    <string name="kaku_loading">Kaku is loading…</string>
    <string name="beta_screen">"Thanks for installing the beta version of Kaku! If you didn't intend to install the beta version, I highly recommend that you go to the Play Store and leave the beta program - the beta version of Kaku may be unstable and more prone to bugs. If you are not in the beta program and but still seeing this message, please let me know right away by e-mailing me below!

If you run into issues (i.e., constant crashes or graphical glitches) in the beta, please let me know at 0xbad1d3a5@gmail.com! Feedback and suggestions are also welcome!

BETA UPDATES:

vLATEST
- Revert Tesseract library update as that was causing vertical OCR recognition issues
- Fresh build from clone

v1.3.72
- Emergency fix for Android 12
- Update Tesseract libraries

v1.3.66
- Stop screen capture when device is put to sleep
- Minor bugfixes

v1.3.62
- Updating beta version of Kaku will longer remove the icon from the home screen after this update
- Improve artist text

v1.3.59
- Temporarily disable ads

v1.3.56
- Minor bugfixes
- Added dialog in tutorial explaining Kaku's permissions

v1.3.55
- No Kaku updates, just backend changes
- Bump Kotlin version, use Triple-T for automated Play Console uploads

v1.3.47
- Fix minor crashes in Kaku

v1.3.46
- Improve recognition of commonly mis-recognized kana such as ー or 一
- Improved normal mode so that the entire sentence can be copied, tap the sides of the normal mode window to scroll

v1.3.45
- Improve recognition of commonly mis-recognized kana such as く or し

v1.3.43
- Add similar kana to swap quick text action in case that OCR engine doesn't give that recommendation

v1.3.42
- Reduce size of tutorial videos

v1.3.40
- Revamped tutorial and shows on first start of the app
- Fix minor bugs

v1.3.38
- Fixed entry ranking issue with dictionary - less common readings of a kanji will rank lower.
- Fixed icon placement bug with select-to-swap actions in certain cases when the status bar / navigation bar is showing.

v1.3.37
- Removed history window. Not ready for prime time and I didn't particularly find it useful.
- Added ability to completely hide Kaku's capture window through the notification.

v1.3.34
- Added history window. This window shows previous kanji that you have looked up.
- You can now share text to Kaku to trigger the popup window as well.

v1.3.33
- One ad added to start screen. Sorry! But it's to help support development. It should be fairly out of the way, but let me know if it causes problems.
- Adding the ad does get rid of the 'Close Capture Window' button, but a reminder to all that you can close Kaku by simply tapping on Kaku's notification in the status bar. If you are unable to close Kaku because the notification is missing, please send me an e-mail!
- Fixed instant mode rotation bug where positioning was incorrect after device rotation.
- Fixed bug where Kaku does not start on some devices (particularly Xiaomi devices).

v1.3.32
- Instant Mode window positioning logic has been implemented. If things look off here, please let me know!

Note that if you try to leave feedback on the Play Store as a beta user, it is not shown to all users."</string>
</resources>
