<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kaku</string>
    <string name="support_text">"Like Kaku? Here's how you can help!"</string>
    <string name="kaku_loading">Kaku is loading…</string>
    <string name="beta_screen">"Thanks for installing the beta version of Kaku! If you didn't intend to install the beta version, I highly recommend that you go to the Play Store and leave the beta program - the beta version of Kaku may be unstable and more prone to bugs.

If you run into issues (i.e., constant crashes or graphical glitches) in the beta, please let me know at 0xbad1d3a5@gmail.com! Feedback and suggestions are also welcome!

BETA UPDATES:

v1.3.39
- Revamped tutorial and shows on first start of the app
- Fix minor bugs

v1.3.38
- Fixed entry ranking issue with dictionary - less common readings of a kanji will rank lower.
- Fixed icon placement bug with select-to-swap actions in certain cases when the status bar / navigation bar is showing.

v1.3.37
- Removed history window. Not ready for prime time and I didn't particularly find it useful.
- Added ability to completely hide Kaku's capture window through the notification.

v1.3.34
- Added history window. This window shows previous kanji that you have looked up.
- You can now share text to Kaku to trigger the popup window as well.

v1.3.33
- One ad added to start screen. Sorry! But it's to help support development. It should be fairly out of the way, but let me know if it causes problems.
- Adding the ad does get rid of the 'Close Capture Window' button, but a reminder to all that you can close Kaku by simply tapping on Kaku's notification in the status bar. If you are unable to close Kaku because the notification is missing, please send me an e-mail!
- Fixed instant mode rotation bug where positioning was incorrect after device rotation.
- Fixed bug where Kaku does not start on some devices (particularly Xiaomi devices).

v1.3.32
- Instant Mode window positioning logic has been implemented. If things look off here, please let me know!

Note that if you try to leave feedback on the Play Store as a beta user, it is not shown to all users."</string>
</resources>
